>> Kyle Simpson: 要将模块引入语法，请导入这些模块，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To bring modules
into your syntax, to import them,
有两种主要的进口方式。
there are two major styles of import.
有一堆变体，但是两种主要的进口风格。
There's a bunch of variations,
but two major styles of import.
一个称为指定的导入语法，您在第 1 行上看到该语法。
One is called the named import
syntax which you see on line 1.
我导出缺省函数，因此在技术上其名称缺省为
I exported the default function, so
technically its name is default from
然后我决定了默认的进口要求
the outside, and then I decided to
name that default import ask on
第 1 行，即现在在我的顶级范围内发生导入的范围，
line 1, which means now in my top level
scope of where the import happened,
我现在有个叫 " 问 " 的标识
I now have an identifier called ask,
它是在模块中绑定到请求函数的引用。
which is reference bound to the ask
function inside of the module.
这就是我们所说的 Java 样式
That's what we sort of referred to
as the Java style of import where
导入意味着将标识导入到您的作用域中。
import means literally to import
identifiers into your scope.
第二个样式，如您在第 7 行上看到的，一般称为名称空间
The second style, as you see on line 7,
is referred to generally as the namespace
输入，即我想获取整个模块并收集所有
import, which is to say I wanna get
this whole module and collect all of
它的内容在一个名称间隔的变量中，在这个例子中称为工作坊。
its contents onto a single name spaced
variable, in this case called workshop.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
I do import * as workshop,
这叫名称空间导入
that's called the namespace import.
那是另一个不同的想法
And that's a different school of thinking,
就是这些模块就像这些名称空间的东西。
which is that modules are like
these namespace things.
我认为这种风格代表了大多数模块的完成
I think that style represents the vast
majority of how modules have been done in
过去 20 年的 JavaScript
JavaScript for the last 20 years.
而命名的进口语法也代表了新的思维学校。
And the named import syntax represents
kinda the new school of thinking.
不是一个是对的，一个是错的，但是
It's not that one is right and
one is wrong, but
他们对你的消费方式有不同的思考方式
they're different ways of thinking
about how you consume stuff.
我当然在营地里喜欢输入一个名称空间，然后我就
I certainly am in the camp that prefers
to import a namespace, and then I
有一个叫车间的东西，然后我又有个东西叫别的东西。
have a thing called workshop, and then I
have another thing called something else.
这就是我的大脑运作方式，有些人喜欢被命名的进口产品，
That's the way my brain works,
some people like the named imports,
都是语法感谢
both syntaxes,thankfully.
他们不会做空间导入和
They weren't gonna do
the name space import and
然后在最后一刻加入
then they added it at the last minute and
我非常感谢，因为这就是我想处理它的方式。
I was so thankful because that's the way
that I would prefer to deal with it.
所以有您的 ES6 模块语法，例如，我们不期望语法
So there's your ES6 module syntax, such
as it is, we're not expecting syntactic
更改，但在节点土地上使用时，会出现各种警告。
changes but there will be a variety of
caveats when you're using it in node land.
而且因为它会在陆地上很受欢迎你可以预料到
And because it's gonna be so popular in
node land, you can expect that those same
caveat 可能也会转至您的浏览器 JavaScript 。
caveats will probably carry over to
your browser JavaScript, as well.
你有问题
You got a question.
>> 扬声器 2: 当您说您喜欢旧的模块样式时，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: When you say you prefer
the old module style you mean,
是否在一个文件中显示模块模式 ?
the revealing module pattern in one file?
>> Kyle Simpson: 函数环绕在几张幻灯片之前。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The function
wrapped around a couple slides ago.
>> 扬声器 2: 谢谢。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Thank you.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Mm-hm.
>> Kyle Simpson: 具体地说，当我要执行模块时，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Specifically
when I'm gonna do a module,
我将模块显示为 UMD 样式模块。
I expose my modules as UMD style modules.
这是通用模块定义。
That's the universal module definition.
它应该在浏览器，模块装入器和节点之间进行交互。
It's supposed to kind of inter-operate
between browsers, module loaders and node.
这就是我选择写的格式。
So that's the format I choose to write in.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，您是否在您的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So whether you
use a syntactic support in your
定义模块的语言，或
language to define your modules, or
你是否选择利用旧的学校展示模块模式
whether you choose to hack it with
the old school revealing module pattern,
这个概念也适用，就是你要组织一套行为，
the same concept applies, which is that
you're organizing a set of behavior into
一个内聚性单元将数据隐藏在其中，并暴露最小必需的 API。
a cohesive unit hiding data in it and
exposing a minimal necessary API.
这就是你想要得到的设计模式。
That's the design pattern
that you wanna get.
然后，就像我说的，这是你能学到的最重要的事情之一
And then, like I said, it’s one of the
most important things that you can learn
有关组织您的 JavaScript的信息。
about organizing your JavaScript.
其实你在里面做什么都不重要
It actually doesn’t matter
what you do on the inside.
如果你真的想这样的话你可以在里面写课
You could write classes all over place on
the inside if that’s how you really wanted
但是你还是想把所有这些行为
to do stuff, but you're still gonna
want to organize all of that behavior
在一个模块中，某人可以将该行为导入到其应用中并使用它。
into a module, so that somebody can import
that behavior into their app and use it.
模块模式一定要留在这里不会去任何地方
Module pattern, is definitely here
to stay, it's not gonna go anywhere.
好了，就这样，有模块模式。
All right, so there you go,
there is the module pattern.
在这个问题上我们对这个问题有了充分的理解
And with that, we now have a full
breadth of understanding of
词法范围核心或主支柱，
the lexical scope core or the main pillar,
这是 JavaScript 语言的主要支柱。
this main pillar of
the JavaScript language.
如果我要在三大支柱中煮沸，这个是最重要的。
And if I were to boil down among the three
pillars, this one is the most important.
它是用这种基本方式触摸所有其他事物的。
It's the one that touches everything
else in such a foundational way.
希望这能让你更好地了解词法技能。
So hopefully that has provided you
a better perspective on lexical skill.